I'd never seen anybody pick up dog poop
until I moved to
Colorado I'd never seen it once did
y'all know they don't do it in movies
did y'all know that you got to watch it
live it's like music you know it's like
if you want it good you got to go to the
park y'all can call me old school call
me what you want but I'm from a place
where we just run over it with a lawn
mower until we can't find it
anymore y'all know what I mean you kind
of circle back around on it and you look
at it and you're like you know what I
think I've diced it up pretty pretty
good and you can always tell how big it
is y'all know I mean you'll hit it you
know and you'll kind of get that little
bounce like that it's like that and then
you'll get a whiff of it I got to Circle
back on that one we're going to have to
hit it one more time that's a bad one
right
there then you go hey did you feed him
twice I mean it's like a speed bump out
here my good I lost the
tire I just never thought I'd see people
bending over
standing behind a golden retriever
that's taken a bigger poop than they've
taken yet just I mean c if you're a good
neighbor you'll catch it before it hits
the ground you know I mean y'all don't
let it hit the grass I'm a good neighbor
I'm a good neighbor you know I am
walking around swinging it in your hand
talking about I might go to TJ Maxx
depends on the weather you know I might
I don't know where my day will go from
here that's wild to me that's I never
dreamed of that I I remember the first
night I was in Denver I had a hard time
falling asleep cuz all I could think
about is what if my dog had diarrhea you
know I didn't see one person at that
park with a ladle how do y'all pick this
up if I see you picking up dog diarrhea
with a bag we're I'm going to go ahead
and call the cops that's it and we're
going to look at your internet browser
Doug cuz you're off the rails out here
that's diarrhea that's a bag my man that
doesn't
work I just don't know how we haven't
come up with a better way to pick it up
yet
I mean we're on hoverboards eating
powdered dinners and we're still picking
this stuff up with Smith's grocery
bags y'all remember like in the third
grade when a little kid would throw up
macaroni and cheese in the hallway and
the janitor he'd come out of the closet
and he' pour this powder all over that
macaroni and cheese and what was once
liquid now turns in and then now he just
sweeps it up now it's just powder and
then he'd go right back into that closet
where is that
powder do you know how much easier are
like you guys don't have to pick up any
more we're going to dust it and kick it
it'll be over I'll go on Shark Tank I'll
do it live I'll make Mark CU and look me
in the eyes we're going to dust it and
kick
it tired of bending over I mean with a
bag I can see through that barely goes
over my hand you
know for